<lml>
	<meta date="">
		<title>First Hour</title>
		<!-- Allow multiple commemorations. ID used by movable hymns. -->
		<commemoration movable="true" id=""></commemoration>
		<commemoration movable="true"></commemoration>
	</meta>
	<service>
		<section heading="Call to Prayer">
			<!-- Should there be an indication of ranking? -->
			<reader>
				Through the prayers of our holy Fathers, Lord Jesus Christ our God,
				have mercy on us. Amen.
				<br />
				Glory to Thee, our God, glory to Thee.
			</reader>
		</section>
		<section heading="Trisagion">
			<reader>
				Heavenly King, O Comforter, the Spirit of truth, Who art everywhere
				present	and fillest all things, O treasury of every good and Bestower
				of life: come and dwell in us, and cleanse us from every stain, and
				save our souls, O Good One.
				<br />
				<repeat times="3">Holy God, Holy Mighty, Holy Immortal, have
					mercy on us.</repeat>
				<br />
				Glory to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit, Both
				now and ever and unto ages of ages. Amen.
				<br />
				All-holy Trinity, have mercy on us. Lord, be gracious unto our sins.
				Master,	pardon our iniquities. Holy One, visit and heal our
				infirmities for Thy Name's sake.
				<br />
				<repeat time="3">Lord, have mercy.</repeat>
				<br />
				Glory to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit, Both
				now and ever and unto ages of ages. Amen.
				<br />
				Our Father, Which art in the Heavens, hallowed be Thy Name. Thy
				Kingdom	come. Thy will be done, on earth as it is in Heaven. Give us
				this day our daily bread. And forgive us our debts, as we forgive our
				debtors. And lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from the
				evil one.
				<br />
				Amen.
				<repeat times="3">Lord, have mercy.</repeat>
				Glory to the Father, and to the
				Son, and to the Holy Spirit, Both now
				and ever and unto ages of
				ages. Amen.
				<br />
			</reader>
			<section heading="Come let us Worship">
				<reader>
					O come, let us worship and fall down before our King and God. O
					come,
					let us worship and fall down before Christ, our King and God. O come,
					let us worship and fall down before Him, Christ the King and our
					God.
				</reader>
			</section>
		</section>
		<section heading="Psalms of the First Hour">
			<!-- Populate psalms from some resource -->
			<reader>
				<psalm numbering="LXX" number="83" />
				<psalm numbering="LXX" number="84" />
				<psalm numbering="LXX" number="85" />
				<psalm numbering="LXX" number="85" verses="17" />
				Glory to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit, Both
				now and ever and unto ages of ages. Amen.
				<br />
				<repeat times="3">Alleluia, alleluia, alleluia: Glory to Thee, O
					God.</repeat>
				<br />
				<repeat times="3">Lord, have mercy.</repeat>
		</section>
		<section heading="Commemoration Hymns of the day">
			Glory to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit.
			<!-- Insert one or more tropars -->
			<troparion moveable="true" id="" tone=""></troparion>
			Both now and ever and unto ages of ages. Amen.
		</reader>
		</section>
		<section heading="Commemoration of the Hour">
			<reader>
				O Thou Who for our sakes wast born of a Virgin, and didst suffer
				crucifixion, O Good One, and didst despoil death by death, and as
				God didst reveal the Ressurection: Disdain them not which Thou hast
				fashioned with Thy hand; show us Thy love for mankind, O Merciful
				One; accept the Theotokos that gave Thee birth, who intercedeth for
				us; and do Thou, our Saviour, save a desparing people.
				<br />
				Deiver us not up utterly, for Thy holy Name's sake, neither disanul
				Thou Thy covenant, and cause not Thy mercy to depart from us, for
				Abraham's sake, Thy beloved, and for Issac's sake, Thy servant, and
				for Israel's, Thy holy one.
				<br />
			</reader>
		</section>
		<section heading="Dismissal">
			<reader>
				<repeat times="3">Holy God, Holy Mighty, Holy Immortal, have
					mercy on us.</repeat>
				Glory to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit, Both
				now and ever and unto ages of ages. Amen.
				<br />
				All-holy Trinity, have mercy on us. Lord, be gracious unto our sins.
				Master, pardon our iniquities. Holy One, visit and heal our
				infirmities for Thy Name's sake.
				<br />
				<repeat times="3">Lord, have mercy.</repeat>
				<br />
				Glory to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit, Both
				now and ever and unto ages of ages. Amen.
				<br />
				Our Father, Which art in the Heavens, hallowed be Thy Name. Thy
				Kingdom come. Thy will be done, on earth as it is in Heaven. Give us
				this day our daily bread. And forgive us our debts, as we forgive
				our debtors. And lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from
				the evil one.
				<br />
				Amen.
				<br />
				As first-fruits of our nature to the Planter of created things, the
				world presenteth the God-bearing martyred Saints in off'ring unto
				Thee, O Lord. Through their entreaties, keep Thy Church in deep
				peace and divine tranquillity, through the pure Theotokos, O Thou
				Who art greatly merciful.
				<br />
				<repeat times="40">Lord, have mercy.</repeat>
				<br />
				Thou Who at all times and at every hour, in Heaven and on earth, art
				worshipped and glorified, O Christ God, Who art long-suffering,
				plenteous in mercy, most compassionate, Who lovest the righteous and
				hast mercy on sinners, Who callest all to salvation through the
				promise of good things to come: receive, O Lord, our prayers at this
				hour, and guide our life toward Thy commandments. Sanctify our
				souls, make chaste our bodies, correct our thoughts, purify our
				intentions, and deliver us from every sorrow, evil, and pain.
				Compass us about with Thy holy Angels, that, guided and guarded by
				their array, we may attain to the unity of faith, and the knowledge
				of Thine unapproachable glory; for blessed art Thou unto the ages of
				ages. Amen.
				<br />
				<repeat times="3">Lord, have mercy.</repeat>
				<br />
				Glory to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit, Both
				now and ever and unto ages of ages. Amen.
				<br />
				More honourable than the Cherubim, and beyond compare more glorious
				than the Seraphim, thee who without corruption gavest birth to God
				the Word, the very Theotokos, thee do we magnify.
				<br />
				In the Name of the Lord, bless. Amen.
				<br />
				O Master, Lord Jesus Christ our God, Who art long-suffering in the
				face of our transgressions, and Who hast brought us even unto this
				present hour, wherin Thou didst hang upon the life-creating Tree,
				and dist make a way into Paradise for the sinners and Thine unworthy
				servants; for we have sinned and committed iniquity, and are not
				worthy to lift up our eyes and behold the height of Heaven, for we
				have abandoned the way of Thy righteousness, and have walked in the
				desires of our hearts. But we beseech Thine incomparable goodness:
				Spare us, O Lord, according to the multitude of Thy mercy, and save
				us for Thy holy Name's sake, for our days have wasted away in
				vanity. Deliver us from the hand of the adversary, and forgive us
				our sins, and mortify our carnal mind; that putting aside the old
				man, we may be clad with the new, and live for Thee, our Master and
				Guardian; and that thus by following in Thy commandments, we may
				attain to rest everlasting, wherein is the dwelling-place of them
				that love Thee, O Christ our God, and unto Thee we send up glory,
				with Thy Father which is without beginning, and Thine All-holy and
				good and life-creating Spirit, now and ever, and unto the ages of
				ages. Amen.
				<br />
				Glory to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit, Both
				now and ever and unto ages of ages. Amen. Lord, have mercy. (Three
				times). Lord, bless.
				<br />
				Through the prayers of our holy Fathers, Lord Jesus Christ our God,
				have mercy on us. Amen.
				<br />
			</reader>
		</section>
	</service>
</lml>